[Music]
Hello friends welcome to my
youtube1 results are out,
we will try to know how the results were,
after that I will try to tell what levels and targets are coming in the chart, let me
tell you
that ICC General Insurance is a
good stock in itself, it is the market leader, so
how are its results, they
affect the entire insurance sector, so we will
discuss the results, after that we will
also do analysis by going to the chart, so stay tuned
with the video and if you liked the video then
like, here I have brought you to Business Line,
friends here you can see,
Lumbard General Insurance has given
good results on net profit of 28%,
friends there has been a jump of 25% from 28%, so let's
move here,
friends, ICC General Insurance post 28.5% net
growth in net profit, first quarter of
the fiscal deficit, insurance product
being impacted across the industry due to
the national lockdown, there was such a
bad impact due to the lockdown, despite this, 28
% means that a good boom has been posted for
The quarter ended June 30, 2020 registered a net
profit of Rs 398 crore against Rs 309 crore
last year.
The premium net was also higher. The
premium earned also
showed a jump of 35%. It was Rs 2323 crore as against Rs
2244 crore last year. Meaning, although the
gross written premium was
down by around 45%. Compared to the gross written premium which was Rs 3394 crore
last year, it was Rs
3560 crore. If we talk about gross direct premium
income, that is, if we talk about GDPI, there has been a
decline in that too, i.e. 5.3% which has
come to Rs 3302 crore which was Rs 347.87 crore last year. If we
talk about the crop segment, if we
include it, then there has been a
decline of 6.2% in the GDP.
You must be aware that all this decline was due to the lockdown
period and
All this decline is being seen due to the ongoing Covid-19 issue. If
you do not know the combined ratio, then let
me tell you that if we
combine the ratio of the outflow money and the expenses incurred in comparison to the premium earned by the company, it has come to 99.7,
which was 100.4 last year. So there is a
slight decline in this as well. If we look at the ratio from Salmon, it has
come to 2.5 times, which
was 2.17 last year, so there is a slight increase in it. So, the
regular requirement is still
much higher than the 1.5 times requirement, so it means it is good, the
situation does not appear to be bad and a
good jump is visible in the net profit.
So friends, we can say that the result has
come out good, we cannot say it is very good,
but it has
come out much better than the estimates. So, due to this, a
huge increase was also seen in such a trend on Friday, so
go to the chart once and tell what are the levels and targets
coming.  I will try that, so
here I have identified some levels for you,
after that there is a fall again and right now the side is
moving a little, if we talk about closing, which is on 17th
July, then the closing was 1288 p, there was a
rise of about %
for good results of this quarter, so right now if we
talk about the levels, then friends if you
look at the lower levels then there is good support at 1230 p
and below it there is support around 25 p and if we
talk about the upper levels then there is a strong
resistance level of 80 p and above that there is
resistance of 440 sorry 1440 1380 and 14140,
so friends if you want to take a position right now then
if you get this stock around 12500 then a
position can be taken in it and by
placing a stop loss of 1230
you can keep it for target till the level of 380, so
friends good risk to reverse reward is 4
in v, so that means you will have a loss below 20 points,
if this 1250 p is available then what
I think if it
comes down a little bit, then this could be a
good opportunity for you to build a position here and by placing a
stop loss of ₹25 or below or in this,
you can create a long position.
In the insurance sector, let me tell you that there is
still a lot of growth
potential left in India, so friends, you must have a stock of the
insurance sector in your portfolio,
so if this is also one of the
best stocks, apart from this, there are ASIC Life Insurance,
HDFC Life Insurance, and SBI Life, then
Lowbar General Insurance is
also good in itself, you will know that it has a
diversified portfolio in many segments,
so friends, we will
go to the NSC website and
I will try to tell you what the details of the business have been.
Here I have
searched ICC Low General Insurance on the NSC website,
you can see that 1288 closing was up 8
%, there was a rise, so if we talk about trading,
738000 shares were traded in which
520000 shares were delivered, deliverable
percentage.  70 p plus, so this is
demonstrating the strength of this company, that the delivery of 70 p,
I am seeing a very good delivery here, so friends,
watch out for this level and if it is found around 1250, then in
my opinion, it will be a very value
buying and as I have mentioned stop loss
1230 and 1125, you can watch out for it,
conduct your study separately and only after that
take some decision and once you take the decision, then
learn to take responsibility for it yourself, so
friends, if you liked this much video then like it
and subscribe to my channel
[Sangeet]